

# Raden Rafly Pradana Kusumah

Bogor, Jawa Barat, 16770 | 0838 9593 8361 | radenraflypradanakusumah@gmail.com https://bit.ly/radenrafly

### **About Me**

I am Raden Rafly Pradana Kusumah, a student majoring in PPLG or Software and Game Development from SMKS Wikrama Bogor. I have Experience as a Fullstack Js and react native with the Collaboraon Team Developer for web front end & back end. I have an interest in a career as a Front End Developer and proficient in Programming Languages.

## **Skills**

- HTML5
- CSS
- JavaScript
- ReactJS
- VueJS
- NextJS
- React Native
- Redux
- Postgresql

- JSON
- PHP
- Mysql
- Laravel
- NodeJS
- ExpressJS
- AdonisJS
- Flutter
- Liblary Styling Web Apps

# **Experience**

#### CV. Kreasi Swala Nusantara (Bogor Selatan, Indonesia)

Freelance Front End Development (September 2023-Desember 2023)

- Developing apps using ReactJS, and NodeJS.
- Leveraged knowledge in ReactJS, NodeJS, JavaScript, Using Github.
- Helping to develop a project Service Travel using ReactJS.

#### Freelance FullStack JS Developer (Bogor, Indonesia)

Freelance FullStack Js (August 2023-August 2023)

- Working on several project.
- Leveraged knowledge in FullStack JavaScript MERN (MongoDB, ExpressJs, NodeJS, ReactJS)
  Using Gitlab, Niaghoster.
- Create Company Profile and Ecommerce Project using Technology MERN.

#### PT.Immobi Solusi Prima (Jakarta Selatan, Indonesia)

Intern FullStack JS (Januari 2023-Juli 2023)

- Developing apps using ReactJS, AdonisJS and NodeJS.
- Leveraged knowledge in ReactJS, React Native, VueJS, NodeJS, AdonisJS, Postgresql, JavaScript, Using Gitlab, Jira.
- Helping to develop a project ERP and Fieldtrack using the FullStack JavaScript.

# InfraDigital Foundation (Jakarta Selatan, Indonesia)

Training (2022)

• Participating in training and obtaining certifications for completing CompTIA Network+

## **Education**

## SMK Wikrama Bogor (2020-2024)

Majoring PPLG

- Participate in Final Assessment Project, Project Work, and Certification HTML CSS
- Creating Static and Dynamic Websites

#### SMPN 2 Cisarua (2017-2020)

Organizing class meeting competition activities between batches with OSIS colleagues

### **Achievement**

## Participated in POSSI Indonesian Language Olympiad

• Received a certificate, and a gold medal.

# **Contact information**

#### **Email:**

radenraflypradanakusumah@gmail.com

Call:

(+62)838-9593-8361

Web:

https://raden.vercel.app